Finding Aid for Paul Winston McCracken papers, 1940-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Paul Winston McCracken papers 1940-2011 1959-1990
McCracken, Paul Winston, 1915-
1 oversize folders
52 linear feet
85311 Aa 2 Ac
The materials in the Paul McCracken Papers relate to his career as an economist and his tenure as a Professor at the University of Michigan's Business School. The collection includes correspondence, published papers, speeches, and newspaper clippings.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was donated by Paul W. McCracken (donor no. 5960 ) over the period of 1977-2006. Additions were received in 2010 and 2013.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Paul Winston McCracken was born in Richland, Iowa on December 29, 1915. He graduated with a bachelor's degree from William Penn College in 1937, and then received both his master's degree and doctorate from Harvard in 1942 and 1948, respectively.
From 1937 until 1940, McCracken taught at Foundation School of Berea College. Between 1942 and 1943 he worked as an economist in the U.S. Department of Commerce. In 1943, he left the Commerce Department to become financial economist and director of research at the Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis. He remained in Minneapolis until 1948, when he moved to Ann Arbor to join the faculty of the University of Michigan's School of Business Administration.
Since coming to the University of Michigan, McCracken, in addition to teaching, has been active as a senior economic advisor to both private industry and government. In the private sector, he advised numerous corporations, and serves on the board of directors of firms as diversified as K-Mart Corporation, Detroit Edison and Texas Instruments. In government, his most notable appointments have been two periods of service on the President's Council of Economic Advisers. President Eisenhower named him a member of the Council in 1956, a position he held until 1959. In 1969 President Nixon appointed McCracken chairman of the CEA, a post McCracken held through 1971. McCracken has also served in a number of lesser governmental advisory posts.
The papers of Paul McCracken have been arranged into ten series: Personal, Correspondence, Publicity and Speeches, U.S. Dept. of Commerce National Economic Unit, President's Council of Economic Advisors, Papers, University Notes, Visual Materials, Wall Street Journal, Sound Recordings, and OV Material.
Subjects:
Council of Economic Advisers (U.S.); Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969.; McCracken, Paul W. (Paul Winston), 1915-2012; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.; University of Michigan--Faculty.; University of Michigan. School of Business Administration.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Council of Economic Advisers (U.S.); McCracken, Paul W. (Paul Winston), 1915-2012
Genre/Form:
Photographs.
- Personal
  The Personal series is arranged alphabetically. It is comprised of personal papers including family letters, certificates, appointments, and invitations/programs from the White House.
  - Appointment Certificates (Box 1)
    (in oversize folder Ac)
  - Appointment Certificate to the Board of Directors Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis, June 11, 1945 (Box 1)
  - Commencement Programs Featuring McCracken as a Speaker, 1961-1980 (Box 1)
  - Dinner Club Meeting, February 18, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Family letters, 1940-1955 (Box 1)
  - White House Invitations and Programs, 1957, 1959, 1969
  - Ann Arbor Hills, 1954 (Box 46)
  - Biographical Information, 1986, 2010 (Box 46)
  - Curriculum Vitae (Box 46)
  - Diary Entries, 1938-1939 (Box 46)
  - Edmund Erza Award, 1966 (Box 46)
  - Home Life Insurance, 1948 (Box 46)
  - Jones, Sidney, L. (Biography Project), 1996 (Box 46)
  - List of Books in Library (Box 46)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 46)
  - University of Michigan Appointment and Relocation, 1947-1948 (Box 46)
  - White House Order of Employment, 1969 (Box 46)
- Correspondence
  The Correspondence series makes up the great bulk of the collection It is arranged by date (usually by year or grouping of years) and then by last name of the sender or the first letter of a corporation. This series dates from 1959 to 2004 with a gap from 1964-1971. The researcher should note that although these chronological subseries might be dated (1985 for example), the files themselves will often contain documents both before and after that date. The correspondence in the series is wide ranging, but it primarily reflects McCracken's work as an economist, consultant, or corporate director. Unfortunately, correspondence from McCracken's years as presidential advisor is not part of the collection. See note at the end for their location.
  - 1959-1960
    - A (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 1)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 1)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Chicago Daily News (Box 1)
    - Committee on Michigan's Economic Future (COMEF) (Box 1)
    - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 1)
    - E (Miscellaneous) (Box 1)
    - F (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 1)
    - G (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Graduate School of Banking (Box 2)
    - H (Miscellaneous) (Box 2)
    - I (Miscellaneous) (Box 2)
    - J (Miscellaneous) (Box 2)
    - K (Miscellaneous) (Box 2)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 2)
    - McCracken, personal correspondence (Box 2)
    - N (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 2)
    - P (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 2)
    - R (Miscellaneous) (Box 2)
    - S (Miscellaneous) (Box 2)
    - U (Miscellaneous) (Box 2)
    - V (Miscellaneous) (Box 2)
    - W-Z (Miscellaneous) (Box 2)
  - 1961-1963
    - American Bankers Association (Box 3)
    - American Enterprise Institute (AEI) (Box 3)
    - American Statistical Association (Box 3)
    - American Telephone and Telegraph Company (A.T.T.) (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor Chamber of Commerce (Box 3)
    - B (Miscellaneous) (Box 3)
    - Board of Pensions of the Presbyterian Church (Box 3)
    - Brookings Institute (Box 3)
    - Brown Brothers, Harriman & Company (Box 3)
    - Burroughs Corporation (Box 3)
    - Carnegie Institute of Technology (Box 3)
    - Chicago Title and Trust Company (Box 3)
    - Chicago Title and Trust Company (Box 3)
    - City Securities Corporation (Box 3)
    - Civil and Defense Mobilization, Office of (Box 3)
    - Colorado, University of (Box 3)
    - Columbia University (Box 3)
    - Committee on Economic Growth (Box 3)
    - Continental Illinois National Bank and Trust Company of Chicago (Box 3)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 3)
    - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 3)
    - Department of Commerce (Box 3)
    - Detroit Bank and Trust Company (Box 3)
    - Distributor's Group (Box 3)
    - Dun and Bradstreet, Inc. (Box 3)
    - E (Miscellaneous) (Box 3)
    - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 3)
    - Economic Development Agency (Box 3)
    - Economic Expansion Advisory Council (Box 3)
    - Economic Growth (see Committee on) (Box 3)
    - Equitable Life Insurance Company (Box 3)
    - Executive Development (Box 3)
    - F (Miscellaneous) (Box 3)
    - Federal Reserve Bank
      - Chicago Branch (Box 3)
      - Cleveland Branch (Box 3)
      - Kansas City Branch (Box 3)
      - Minneapolis Branch (Box 3)
      - New York Branch (Box 3)
      - Philadelphia Branch (Box 3)
    - Federal Reserve System (Box 3)
    - First Presbyterian Church (Box 3)
    - Florida State University (Box 3)
    - First National Bank of Chicago (Box 3)
    - First National City Bank of New York (Box 3)
    - Ford Motor Company (Box 3)
    - G (Miscellaneous) (Box 3)
    - General Electric Company (Box 3)
    - General Motors Corporation
      - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
      - General Motors Acceptance Corporation, New York (Box 3)
    - Government Printing Office (Box 3)
    - Group Securities, Incorporated (Box 3)
    - H (Miscellaneous) (Box 3)
    - Harris Trust and Savings Bank (Box 3)
    - Harvard University (Box 3)
    - I (Miscellaneous) (Box 3)
    - India Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Illinois, University of (Box 3)
    - Industrial College of the Armed Forces (Box 3)
    - Institute of Science and Technology (Box 3)
    - Institute for Social Research (Box 3)
    - International Business Machines Corporation (Box 3)
    - International Business Program (Box 3)
    - International Monetary Fund (Box 3)
    - J (Miscellaneous) (Box 3)
    - Japan (Box 3)
    - Joint Economic Committee of Congress (Box 4)
    - K (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - Kobe, Professor Susumu (Institute for Research in Productivity) (Box 4)
    - Langum, John K. (Box 4)
    - Little, Arthur D., organization (Box 4)
    - Mc (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - McCracken, Paul, personal file (Box 4)
    - McGraw-Hill Publishing Company (Box 4)
    - Macalester College, St. Paul, Minnesota (Box 4)
    - Machinery and Allied Products Institute (Box 4)
    - MacMillan Company (Box 4)
    - Manufacturers Trust Company (Box 4)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company (Box 4)
    - Michigan Bankers Association (Box 4)
    - Michigan Bell Telephone Company (Box 4)
    - Michigan State University (Box 4)
    - Michigan, University of (see University of Michigan) (Box 4)
    - Minnesota, University of (Box 4)
    - Missouri, University of (Box 4)
    - Morgan, Stanley (Box 4)
    - Morris, Robert, Associates (Box 4)
    - N (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - National Association of Mutual Savings Banks (Box 4)
    - National Bank of Detroit (Box 4)
    - National Bank and Trust Company, Ann Arbor (Box 4)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc.
      - Miscellaneous file (Box 4)
      - Advisory Committee on Economic Research, Inc. (Box 4)
      - Universities, National Committee for Economic Research (Box 4)
    - National Industrial Conference Board (Box 4)
    - National Presbyterian Church (Box 4)
    - Northern Trust Company (Box 4)
    - O (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - P (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - Perfect Circle Corporation, John Senn letters (Box 4)
    - Philadelphia National Bank (Box 4)
    - R (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - Radiation, Incorporated (Box 4)
    - Recommendation of students (Box 4)
    - Redpath, Robert U., Jr. (Box 4)
    - Regional Economic Science Committee (Box 4)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 4)
    - Request for Room Reservations (Box 4)
    - Robinson Newcomb Associates, Washington D.C. law firm (Box 4)
    - Ronald Press Company (Box 4)
    - S (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - Scientific Club (Box 4)
    - Sears, Roebuck and Company (Box 4)
    - Socony Mobile Oil Company (Box 4)
    - Standard Oil Company of New Jersey (Box 4)
    - Stanford University (Box 4)
    - T (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - Tarnowsky, Ivan, Committee on Cash Flow (Box 4)
    - Texaco, Incorporated (Box 4)
    - Treasury Department (Box 4)
    - U (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - Union Trust company (Box 4)
    - University Center for Adult Education (Box 4)
    - University of Michigan correspondence (Box 4)
    - Upjohn Corporation (Box 4)
    - V (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - W (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - Water Refining Company (Box 4)
    - Wayne National Life Insurance Company (Box 4)
    - Wayne State University (Box 4)
    - William Penn College (Box 4)
    - Win Schuler's Restaurants, Inc. (Box 4)
    - Y (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
    - Z (Miscellaneous) (Box 4)
  - 1972
    - A (Miscellaneous) (Box 5)
    - American Enterprise Institute, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - B (Miscellaneous) (Box 5)
    - Board Refusals (Box 5)
    - C (Miscellaneous) (Box 5)
    - Conference Board (Box 5)
    - Council of Economic Advisors (Box 5)
    - F (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 5)
    - First National Bank of Chicago (Box 5)
    - G (Miscellaneous) (Box 5)
    - H (Miscellaneous) (Box 5)
    - J (Miscellaneous) (Box 5)
    - Japan Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Japan, International Economic Interdependence, May 1972 (Box 5)
    - L (Miscellaneous) (Box 5)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Memoranda received (Box 6)
    - Michigan, University of, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - National Bank of Detroit (Box 6)
    - P (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Pacific Coast Banking School (Box 6)
    - S (Miscellaneous) (Box 6)
    - Tax Foundation, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - W (Miscellaneous) (Box 6)
    - Water Refining Company, Inc., 2 folders (Box 6)
  - 1973
    - A (Miscellaneous) (Box 6)
    - Albion College, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - American Enterprise Institute, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 4 folders (Box 7)
    - C (Miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - E (Miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - Economic Expansion Council, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Energy Commission, 4 folders (Box 7)
    - F (Miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - Foreign correspondence (Box 7)
    - G (Miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - H (Miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - Harris-Intertype Corporation (Box 7)
    - J (Miscellaneous) (Box 7)
    - Japan Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - K (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Kresge (S.S.) Company, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - L (Miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - Layman's National Bible Week, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Lincoln National Corporation, Fort Wayne, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - M (Miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - N (Miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - O (Miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - P (Miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - R (Miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 3 folders (Box 8)
    - U (Miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - U.S.S.R. Correspondence (Box 8)
    - W (Miscellaneous) (Box 8)
    - Water Refining and Water Facts Consortium (Box 8)
    - Youth for Understanding, 4 folders (Box 8)
  - 1974
    - Albion College (Box 9)
    - American Enterprise Institute, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 4 folders (Box 9)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Congress, U.S. Senate (Box 9)
    - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Detroit Edison, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - E (Miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - F (Miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Foreign correspondence (Box 9)
    - G (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Government Departments, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - H (Miscellaneous), 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Harvard Visiting Committee (Box 10)
    - I (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Japan Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - K (Miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - L (Miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Memoranda, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Mc (Miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - McCracken, Paul, personal, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - N (Miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - O (Miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - P (Miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - R (Miscellaneous), 3 folders (Box 10)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Standard Oil Company, Cleveland, 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Survey Research Center (includes earlier material) (Box 11)
    - T (Miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 11)
    - Trilateral Commission, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - V (Miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - W (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Wall Street Journal, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - White House Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 11)
    - White House Memoranda, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - [Correspondence series continued in box 17 and 46] (Box 11)
  - ca. 1970-1975 (primarily 1974-1975)
    - A (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 17)
    - B (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - C (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Committee for Economic Development (Box 17)
    - Congress and Senate (Box 17)
    - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Dinner club (Box 17)
    - E (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Earhart Foundation (Box 17)
    - Economic Action Council (Box 17)
    - Special Commission on Energy (Box 17)
    - F (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Federal Reserve System Board of Governors (Box 17)
    - Foreign correspondence (Box 17)
    - G (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - H (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Investors Group of Companies (Box 17)
    - J (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Japan Correspondence (Box 17)
    - K (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - L (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - M (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Memoranda received (Box 17)
    - Memoranda sent (Box 17)
    - P (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - R (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Richardson-Merrell, Inc. (Box 17)
    - S (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - State Department (Box 17)
    - Treasury Department (Box 17)
    - W.E. Upjohn Institute for Employment Research (Box 17)
    - W (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Water Refining Company (Box 17)
    - William Penn College (Box 17)
    - Y (Miscellaneous) (Box 17)
  - ca. 1972-1977 (primarily 1976)
    - A (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Alexander Hamilton Life Insurance Company (Box 18)
    - American Economic Association (Box 18)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 18)
    - American Telephone and Telegraph (Box 18)
    - Atlantic Council (Box 18)
    - B (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Brookings Institute (Box 18)
    - C (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Citizens for Control of Federal Spending (Box 18)
    - Committee for Economic Development (Box 18)
    - Com-Share Inc. (Box 18)
    - Consolidated Food Corporation (Box 18)
    - Congress and Senate (Box 18)
    - Congressional Budget (Box 18)
    - Cosmos club (Box 18)
    - Council of Economic Advisers (Box 18)
    - Court, Andrew (Box 18)
    - Critical Choices Committee (Box 18)
    - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - E (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Earhart Foundation (Box 18)
    - Economic Action Council of Michigan (Box 18)
    - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 18)
    - Electrical Alternatives (Governor's Advisory Commission on Electric Power Alternatives) (Box 18)
    - F (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 18)
    - General Motors (Box 18)
    - Government Departments (Box 18)
    - H (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Harvard Visiting Committee (Box 18)
    - Investors Group of Companies (Box 18)
    - J (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Japan Correspondence (Box 18)
    - K (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Kresge, S.S. Company (Box 18)
    - L (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Livingston Business Outlook (Box 18)
    - M (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - McCracken personal (Box 18)
    - Memoranda Received (Box 18)
    - Mont Pelerin Society (Box 18)
    - N (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - National Research Council Building Advisory Board (Box 18)
    - Newspapers clippings (Box 18)
    - O (Miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) (Box 18)
    - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development-Economic Growth Study (Box 19)
    - P (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Pierpont Committee (Box 19)
    - Proctor and Gamble (Box 19)
    - R (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Recommendations (Box 19)
    - S (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Sindlinger Reports (Box 19)
    - T (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 19)
    - U (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - United Nations Committees (Box 19)
    - W (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - White House (Box 19)
    - Z (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
  - ca. 1976-77 (primarily 1977)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 19)
    - Atwell, Albert (Box 19)
    - B (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - C (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Committee for Economic Development (Box 19)
    - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - F (Miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 19)
    - Kresge, S.S. Company (Box 19)
    - Lincoln National Corporation (Box 19)
    - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development-Economic Growth Study (Box 19)
    - State Department (Box 19)
    - Texas Instruments, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - ca. 1976-1979 (primarily 1978)
    - A (Miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 20)
    - AT & T (includes earlier material) (Box 20)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 20)
    - C (Miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - E (Miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - F (Miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 20)
    - G (Miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - H (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 20)
    - I (Miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - J (Miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Japan Correspondence (Box 20)
    - L (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 20)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Mc (Miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Memoranda Received (Box 21)
    - Memoranda Sent (Box 21)
    - N (Miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - P (Miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - R (Miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 21)
    - T (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Treasury Department (Box 21)
    - W (Miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - William Penn College (Box 21)
    - Woodrow Wilson Center (Box 21)
    - Unprocessed, 1978 (1986 accession) (Box 21)
  - ca. 1976-1981 (primarily 1979)
    - A (Miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 22)
    - B (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - C (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - E (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - F (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - G (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - H (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - International Management and Development Institute (IDMI), 1976-1979, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - J (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Japan, 1979-1981, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - K (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - L (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - M (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - N (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - O (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - P (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - R (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Richardson-Merrell, Inc. (includes earlier material) (Box 22)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 22)
    - T (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - U (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - V (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - W-Z (Miscellaneous) (Box 22)
  - 1979-1982 1980
    - A (Miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Albion College Board of Trustees (Box 23)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 23)
    - B (Miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Bush, George (includes earlier material) (Box 23)
    - C (Miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Detroit Economic Club (Box 23)
    - E (Miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - F (Miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 23)
    - Fowler-McCracken Commission, 3 folders (Box 23)
    - G (Miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - H (Miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - I (Miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - International Management and Development Institute, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - J (Miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - K (Miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - L (Miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - M (Miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Mc (Miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Memoranda Received, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Memoranda Sent (Box 24)
    - N (Miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - P (Miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - R (Miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 24)
    - T (Miscellaneous) (Box 24)
  - 1981
    - Tax Foundation, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - U (Miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - University Musical Society (largely correspondence with Gail W. Rector) (Box 25)
    - U.S. Congress, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - V (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - W-Z (Miscellaneous), 2 folders (Box 25)
    - William Penn College (Box 25)
    - Woodrow Wilson Center, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - A (Box 25)
    - American Enterprise (Box 25)
    - B (Box 25)
    - C (Box 25)
    - D (Box 25)
    - E (Box 25)
    - Economic Coordinating Group (Box 25)
    - F (Box 25)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 25)
    - G (Box 27)
    - General Motors (Box 27)
    - H (Box 27)
    - I (Box 27)
    - Inflation Policy Task Force, 1980-1983 (later Committee to Fight Inflation) (Box 27)
    - International Management and Development Institute (Box 27)
    - J (Box 27)
    - K (Box 27)
    - L (Box 27)
    - M (Box 27)
    - Memoranda Received (Box 27)
    - Memoranda Sent (Box 27)
    - N (Box 27)
    - NAACP, 1981 (Box 27)
    - R (Box 27)
    - S (Box 27)